<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sam Robbins&#39; Website on devKS</title>
    <link>https://kyungshik.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sam Robbins&#39; Website on devKS</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 15:26:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kyungshik.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Experience</title>
      <link>https://kyungshik.github.io/blog/third-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 16:28:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kyungshik.github.io/blog/third-blog/</guid>
      <description>주식회사 OOOOO 서비스기획부 사원 청년 맞춤형 이사 플랫폼 2021.01 - 2021.10 IoT-Ai 연계 홈서비스 사업 기획, 비대면 이사 견적시스템 앱 화면 설계  유한회사 OOOOO 서비스기획부 사원 기업형 블록체인 서비스 해외 기획부 2018.11 - 2020.03 1 미국, Microsoft Inspire: 한국형 지역화폐 홍보 및 해외수출 2. 중국, 베이징: 해외 투자 유치를 위한 기업 설명회 3. 베트남, Asia Blockchain Consensus Summit: 기업형 블록체인 플랫폼 해외영업 청소년을 위한 4차 산업혁명 교육 4. 인도네시아, SE-Asia Blockchain Summit: 동남아시아 기반 기업형 블록체인 생태계 논의, 자사 플랫폼 해외영업 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Portfolio Website</title>
      <link>https://kyungshik.github.io/portfolio/hugo-portfolio-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kyungshik.github.io/portfolio/hugo-portfolio-website/</guid>
      <description>I created my portfolio website using Hugo and UIKit, it serves as an online resume containing all my work.
This has been created as a theme so that others can use and adapt it.
Sections Homepage The homepage provides the basic information about you, including links to social media, skills you have, things you&amp;rsquo;ve done and your education. This page makes good use of UIKit grid and cards for organising all the information and ensuring it is responsive to work on mobile devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team project without GitHub</title>
      <link>https://kyungshik.github.io/portfolio/example-team-no-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kyungshik.github.io/portfolio/example-team-no-github/</guid>
      <description>This is some content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making a new Website</title>
      <link>https://kyungshik.github.io/blog/first-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kyungshik.github.io/blog/first-blog/</guid>
      <description>For a long time this website has had a couple of links to contact me, but those days are over.
Now I have a brand new Hugo website with a custom written theme complete with
 A homepage with more social links, and description of my skills An about page with description of who I am A portfolio page to showcase all my projects A blog  Why Hugo? The first question is why a site builder?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
